=== Uptolike Share Buttons ===
Contributors: na1vez
Tags: +1, AddThis, social buttons, bookmark, bookmarking, like, share, share button, sharing, social bookmarking, social bookmarks, social buttons
Requires at least: 3.0.1
Tested up to: 3.9.1
Stable tag: 1.2.2
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

Uptolike Share Buttons - social bookmarking widget with sharing statistics.

== Description ==
**What Can You Do With UpToLike Share Buttons?**

* Create custom buttons that will visually appeal to users
* Easily manage social activity online
* Increase online engagement through Shares and Likes
* Attract new visitors from social networks
* Collect and analyze the social activity of users
* Adjust content strategy based on analytics

UpToLike is a single interface from which you can manage the appearance and efficiency of social buttons on your site, as well as collect and analyze statistics on
likes, shares, returns, new users, sources of social traffic, and more.

**Which social networks does UpToLike Share Buttons support?**

UpToLike is compatible with 25 popular social networking sites. It supports the following functions: Bookmark, Print, Email, Follow, etc.

**Unique Functions of UpToLike Share Buttons**

* Customization of social buttons:

  1. 3 different shapes
  2. 6 sizes
  3. Hover effect (increase, clockwise rotation)
  4. 11 button styles
  5. Button background
  6. Text color
  7. Text size of the counter

* Social Media Following
* Automatic text selection: the system gives you the option to share a highlighted piece of text on a social network

* Gathering unique statistics of social media activity

**What statistics does UpToLike collect?**

* Number of Likes and Shares on site during the selected period
* Number of users attracted because of Likes and Shares
* Separation of traffic on social networks
* Per-page site activity: how many Likes and Shares for each individual page, and how many new visitors came to each page

== Installation ==
1. Go to Plugins -> Add New
2. Search for Uptolike
3. Install the plugin called \"Uptolike Share Buttons\" and activate it
4. Adjust your settings
5. Request and fill the secret key field, if you want to receive the statistics
6. Enjoy!

== Frequently Asked Questions ==
Answers to Frequently Asked Questions you can find at http://uptolike.ru/faq

== Screenshots ==
1. Customizing sharing buttons
2. Buttons appearance
3. Traffic and sharing statistics

== Changelog ==
= 1.2.2 =
* Enhancement: cut spaces in cryptkey field
* Enhancement: feedback link
* Enhancement: access to plugins by top menu item

= 1.2.1 =
* Bug Fix: minor bug fixes

= 1.2.0 =
* Enhancement: user registration.

= 1.0.0 =
* Initial release
